this problem has given us some data
and asked us to create a nested hash
we can see that we have a car which has
a type a color
and a year as well as a truck with a
type a color
and a year let's begin
just by creating hashes for each of
these
sets of data
[Music]
now we can see that we have one hash on
line one holding the data of a car
and a second hash on line two holding
the data associated with a truck
hash values can be any object including
a hash so in order to associate this
first hash with a car
we can actually make car the key
and have our hash be the associated
value
and we'll do the same thing with the
truck
now we just need to wrap our key value
pairs
in curly braces and separate them with a
comma
and we have a nested hash